payentry.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy | Payentry

### Introduction

At Payentry or MPAY, we are committed to your privacy. This statement describes the information we collect from our online visitors and how we use this information. Our Privacy Policy pertains to all the Payentry or MPAY family of websites including our hosted application sites, such as the Payentry.com family (referred to collectively in this Privacy Policy as the “Service”).

### The Information We Collect

Unless stated otherwise in this Privacy Policy, we only collect personally identifiable information from you if you provide this information to us. Personally identifiable information is information that could be used to identify you, such as your name, address, company name, e-mail address, and user ID.

Some of our websites, like many commercial websites, utilize “cookies” for the purpose of enhancing your customer experience while using our websites. Cookies are small files that websites put on your computer when you visit that website. Cookies are designed to remember user preferences that have been set during a visit so when a user returns, the next visit will be more efficient. Some of our application websites may use cookies to remember and customize application settings and preferences associated with a customer’s user ID.

We also collect non-personally identifiable information through our Internet log files, which record data such as user IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of the Service.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and accuracy, and ensure the proper use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and operational procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We secure the personally identifiable information you provide on servers located in controlled, secure environments, protected from unauthorized access, use, or alteration. Only employees and contractors who need access to your information to perform a specific task or function are granted access to such information. All Payentry or MPAY employees must abide by this Privacy Policy. Any employee who violates this Privacy Policy may be subject to disciplinary action, including termination.

Notwithstanding the above commitments to protect your information (including personally identifiable information) from loss, misuse or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you provide your information to us at your own risk.

### How We Use Your Information

We may use your personally identifiable information as required to administer the Service, including in the following situations:

  * To respond to inquiries regarding sales, products, and/or service.
  * To perform specific tasks that are necessary to service your account.
  * To provide the ability for our users to self-service their accounts.
  * To enhance customer experience when using our websites.

We may use non-personally identifiable information to analyze trends, to administer the Service, to monitor the use of the Service, and to gather general demographic information. We may link this information to personally identifiable information for these and other purposes such as personalizing your experience on the Service and evaluating our Services in general.

### Disclosing Information to Third Parties

_**Laws and Legal Rights**_

We may disclose your information (including personally identifiable information) if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with an applicable statute, regulation, rule or law, a subpoena, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other valid legal process. We may disclose personally identifiable information in special circumstances when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms and Conditions for our Services, or to protect the safety and/or security of our users, Payentry or MPAY, or the general public.

_**Third Parties Generally**_

We may provide to third parties information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted, including where such information is combined with similar information of other users of the Service. For example, we might inform third parties regarding traffic patterns, the number of unique users who visit the Service, the average number of employees employed by our customers, the demographic breakdown of our registered users of the Service, or the products and/or services purchased using the Service and the vendors of such products and services. The third parties to which we may provide this information may include potential or actual advertisers, providers of advertising products or services (including vendors and website tracking services), commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties.

_**Outside Contractors**_

We may employ independent contractors, vendors, and suppliers (collectively, “Outside Contractors”) to provide specific services and products related to the Service, such as hosting and maintaining the Service, providing credit card processing and fraud screening, and developing applications for the Service and e-mail services. In the course of providing products or services to us, these Outside Contractors may sometimes have limited access to information collected on the Service, including your personally identifiable information. We also require that these contractors (1) protect the privacy of your personally identifiable information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (2) not use or disclose your personally identifiable information for any purpose other than providing us with the products or services for which we contracted.

_**Integrated Third Party Services**_

In some cases, our products and services may be integrated with the products and services of third parties for the purpose of providing further benefits and features to our clients. Information, including personally identifiable information, may be passed back and forth between our Service and the third party’s products and services. By submitting the requested information, you affirmatively consent to have that information shared with such third parties. While we seek only to work with partners that employ similar techniques for data privacy as we do, we are not responsible for their privacy practices. Accordingly, we encourage you to ask your provider for details on their privacy practices, to be aware when the Service links to such third parties’ sites and to read the privacy policies or statements of each and every such third party. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Service.

_**Third Party Sellers**_

In addition, through the Service, you may be given the opportunity to purchase (or to obtain more information regarding) certain content, products or services that are sold by parties other than us (collectively, “Merchants”). We will attempt to make it clear to you when you are dealing with a Merchant by opening a new browser or otherwise notifying you that you are leaving the Service. For example, if you see a phrase such as “powered by” or “brought to you by” followed by the name of a person or company other than the Service, then you are likely on, or about to enter, a Web site hosted or operated by a person or company other than us. Merchants may request that you submit certain information to them in order to purchase their products or services or to obtain additional information from them. By submitting the requested information, you affirmatively consent to have that information shared with the Merchant. This information is used by the Merchant and may be subject to a different privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of Merchants. We encourage you to be aware when the Service links to Merchants’ Web sites and to read the privacy policies or statements of each and every Merchant Web site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Service. We do not otherwise share or disclose your personally identifiable information to Merchants.

_**Employee Data**_

In some cases, the data we host is owned by third parties that are responsible for servicing their own clients. Examples of these third parties may include payroll service bureaus, insurance companies, or other third party administrators. While the same security measures described above apply to the information that we host for these parties, we are not responsible for their privacy practices. Please contact your provider for more information regarding their own privacy practices. Furthermore, if you are a client of one of these third parties, you will also need to contact them to update your information. If the features exist within the application to update your account online, you may do so as well.

_**Sale of Business**_

We reserve the right to transfer information to a third party in the event of a sale, merger or other transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of Payentry or MPAY provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

_**Affiliates**_

We may disclose information (including personally identifiable information) about you to our Affiliates. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Affiliates” means any person or entity which directly or indirectly controls, is controlled by or is under common control with Payentry or MPAY, whether by ownership or otherwise. Any information relating to you that we provide to our Affiliates will be treated by those Affiliates in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

You should be aware that we may revise this Privacy Policy at any time and that such revisions may result in additional uses or disclosures of your personally identifiable information. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on the Service so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We may also make non-significant changes to this Privacy Policy that generally will not affect our use of your personally identifiable information. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Service.

### How to Update Your Information

You may view and/or modify your personal identifiable information at any time by logging into your account or by contacting us using the appropriate contact link provided on the website.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us using any of the following:

Payentry or MPAY, Inc.  
Attn. Customer Care – Privacy Policy  
9920 Kincey Ave Suite 110  
Huntersville, NC 28078

Phone: (888) 632-2940  
Email: [publicrelations@mpay.com](mailto:publicrelations@mpay.com) (Not for technical support)

**For login assistance or technical support, please contact your employer or payroll administrator** **.**
